

Samih Youssef

Web and mobile developer

CONTACT

+212 6 22 31 36 79

youssefsamih.tk

youssef.samih97@gmail.com

in youssef-samih

TRAINING

PUBLIC PROFESSIONAL LICENSE IN MEDICAL COMPUTING
University FS ain Chock
2018 – 2019

DIPLOME TS IN INFOMMATIC DEVELOPMENT

ISTA SPECIALIZED IN APPLIED TECHNOLOGY 2015 – 2017

DIPLOME BACCALAUREAT SVT

High school Omar Ibn Al Khatab 2014 – 2015

LANGUAGES

✓ Anglais : Well

✓ Arabe : Current

✓ French : Beginner

PROFILE

2 year and 2 months as a web and mobile developer at degitale agency and web marketing webeuz in the enumeration of recent technologies in development I am more passionate about all that corresponds to javascript development and these frameworks such as react, js node, express, and also wordpress, symfony.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cloudme International | Freelance Mobile Développer

Juin. 2019 - Nov. 2019

Tasks performed, development new module in team an open source cms SIBERIAN like wordpress for simplify making mobile App for android and ios (see my portfolio for live demo and details)

WEBEUZ | Web and Mobile Développer

Nov. 2017 - Juin. 2019

Tasks performed, back-end development of mobile applications (android and ios) with Node js and front-end with React native and redux: like Logistic 24, Safkati, fresh to delivery, App e-Kaizen App Medix Training (in the Play Store); Web application development ohmylead.com (lead management); (see my portfolio for more details)...

WEBEUZ | Intern Web Developer

August. 2017 - Oct. 2017

Tasks performed, Plugin development and wordpress theme; Development of wordpress sites; application creation web in php and mysql (back-end); Participate as a team in the creation of website recrute.endev.ma

SKILLS

Php, C, C++, JavaScript

React, React native, Redux,
Bootstrap, Symfony, JQuery,
Node js (express)

HTML, CSS

SQL Server, MySQL,

CERTIFICATION

Firebase, MongoDB

MCPS sur HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery; 4 MCPS Sur SQL Server; SoloLearn En PHP; Openclassroom In SYMFONY, Information system & React native.